Mohamed Aziz Ben Rejeb

🗷 Azizbenrejen25@hotmail.com 🛘 +216 21 495 019 🛅 https://www.linkedin.com/in/mohamed-aziz-ben-rejeb-1b2483198/ 📤 https://benrejeb.com

SUMMARY

Web developer and embadded system student with 1 years of experience. Proven understanding of web development and database management. Strong data visualization skills with proficiency in Tableau. Seeking a position as web developer to design and develop high-quality websites and applications.

EXPERIENCE

Intership

STIP consists of developing an employee management platform.

• Front-end: HTML,CSS,BOOTSTRAP,AJAX,JS

P. I. PHP 1903

• Back-end : PHP,JSON

Freelance

Fiverr

February 2021 - Present, Tunis, Sousse

January 2022 - February 2022, Tunis, Sousse

 $\boldsymbol{\cdot}$ Designed and coded a responsive website from scratch.

Intership LEADERSHIFT

January 2020 - February 2022, Tunis, Sousse

•

EDUCATION

bachelor degree in embedded and mobile systems

institut supérieur des etudes technologiques de sousse · Tunis, Sousse · 2023

CERTIFICATIONS

IELTS

british council · 2019

DELF B2

Campus France · 2019